SMITARANI SATAPATHY

HR Manager

From sourcing qualified candidates to administering benefits, my focus through my career has been on attracting and retaining the best talent. An enthusiastic team player who strives to contribute best practice, standards compliant approaches wherever possible. Having total 6.3 years of work experience, which includes 4.3 years' experience in HR Generalist profile and 2 years of experience in IT industry.





8249718725



WORK EXPERIENCE

HR Manager

Allin Info Systems Pvt Ltd

08/2019 - Present, Noida Website Designing Company

Talent Acquisition, Onboarding employee, Payroll processing, Statutory compliances, Employment engagement, Performance Appraisal, HRMS, Training & Development, Update Policies

Contact: 093131 32789

Asst HR manager

Radicle IT solutions

02/2017 - 07/2019, Hydrabad Software Development Company

In house Recruitment, Attendance Management, PMS, Induction prog, Conduct Disciplinary actions, Maintaining employee records, PF & ESI, Update policies, Employment Recreation & Engagement

Contact: 040 - 69902266 - HR Dept

IT Security Analyst

IBM, Bangalore

03/2015 - 12/2016.

Software Company

Security compliance Team, NCI Raising, CIRAT, Health checking of Servers, Patch Management, IBM big fix tool, Server activation

CERTIFICATES

- Prevention of Sexual exploitation and abuse (Unicef)
- Communication and Interpersonal Skill
- People Analytics (Coursera)
- Human Resource Management Capstone. (Coursera)
- Managing Employee Performance

EDUCATION

Degree	Institution	Year	Percentage
PGDHRM	SCDL,Pune	2020	75%
B.TECH Applied Electronics & Instrumentation	BPUT, Odisha	2013	7.2 CGPA
12th (C.B.S.E)	Kendriya Vidyalaya, Berhampur	2008	61%
10th (C.B.S.E)	Kendriya Vidyalaya, Berhampur	2006	83%

SKILLS

Communication skills, Negotiation Skill Empathetic Skills, Analytical Driven & Oriented Perseverance & motivated, Administrative expert HRMS Knowledge and Expertise Decision Making skills, Teamwork, HR Policies & SOPs Updatation

HONOR AWARDS

- Star Performer, (06/2017 07/2017) (Radicle IT solutions)
- College Placement coordinator,
- Participated in all India Youth Parliament
- Qualified in TGS,(Army) from College

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

HelpAge India member Organization 08/2004 - 04/2008, Berhampur

Part of Food Distribution Camp (covid period)

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Odiya

INTERESTS

Reading Books, Dancing, Swimming, Listening to Music, Exploring Scifi movies

PERSONAL DETAILS

Marital status—Married DOB- 13.06.1990 www.linkedin.com/in/smita-satapathy-1990